DAVID CASTILLO MORA – BILINGUAL (ENGLISH / SPANISH) Python | Java | C# | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | .Net MVC | SQL Server

Davidcm2803@gmail.com - 64402488

Summary

Technical Support Specialist with 3+ years of experience in high-volume customer service and technical support. Expert in managing 30+ daily calls, handling COVID-19 leave issues, and resolving software and hardware problems. Proven track record in improving service delivery and efficiency. Seeking an IT support role to apply problem-solving skills and enhance customer satisfaction.

> Here is my own portfolio, check it out so you can get to know me better. https://portafolio-david-roan.vercel.app/

SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS: - Effective Communication - Teamwork - Problem Solving - Adaptability - Time Management - Empathy -Leadership - Critical Thinking - Interpersonal Skills - Creativity

TECHINAL SKILLS: - Python - Java - C# - JavaScript - HTML - CSS - Oracle Cloud - SQL Server - SQL Management -Firebase - .Net MVC

EXPERIENCE

CALL CENTER

Amazon CRC 2021-2022

Assisted U.S. Amazon employees with Covid-19 medical leave requests, ensuring timely claim approvals and benefits, leading to higher employee satisfaction and streamlined processes.

- Gained expertise in soft skills, including empathy, improved English communication (oral and written), and managed a high volume of calls and cases.
- Enhanced call quality by empathetically addressing employee concerns and optimizing processes to better meet customer needs.
- Achieved a 30% improvement in handle time, enabling the resolution of twice as many cases within the same time frame, along with strong customer satisfaction metrics.

TECHINAL SUPPORT

Shyft Global Services 2022-Currently

Back Office Support Specialist assisting field engineers in sourcing and requesting technological parts for customers in the United States

- Developed expertise in technological parts, inventory processes, and software troubleshooting by collaborating closely with field engineers and made me learn teamwork.
- Streamlined processes for creating cases and requesting parts, significantly reducing response times and improving efficiency.
- Enhanced team metrics optimized global inventory management, and improved service delivery for customers in the US, Canada, and Japan.

EDUCATION

Centro Educativo Adventista Bilingue de Costa Rica

2015-2020

• High School Diploma

Centro Cultural Británico

2020-2021

• English Studies B2+

Universidad Centroamericana de Ciencia y Tecnología

2022-Currently

• System Engineering

CERTIFICATES

- Java Essential Training | LinkedIn Learning
- Fundamentals of Mathematics: Useful Everyday
 Applications | LinkedIn Learning
- Java Advanced 2 | LinkedIn Learning

- Learning C# | LinkedIn Learning
- C# Advanced: Object-Oriented Programming | LinkedIn Learning
- Mindfulness for Beginners | LinkedIn Learning